[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "What's your next great idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I was thinking about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Do you know any of the other homeowners whose houses have been affected, Jude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yes, we do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jude"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Are they all showing the same kind of stiff upper lip spirit that you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "One of them at least was that we talked to, because he's the one that came around after the fireman to tell us if they were having to check all of the water lines.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What are the -- what are the experts telling you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Right now, not much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Are you going to stay there, Richard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "That's an unbelievable analogy to make, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Those are your words.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Why is it uncanny other than they're two young black boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I'm going to try again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "But you go on to say liberal media should ask if what these two black teens did to a woman and baby is the reason people think blacks might be risky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Of him flicking the bird?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "But you know why they're angry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Are you going to carry on tweeting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "They indict him with photographs of Trayvon Martin that don't accurately portray the person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "But do you accept that what you've done is not helpful to George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I -- of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you think he'll be out in a year's time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I don't think it makes any sense to take a guy who's number one in the time slot, even though all the TV critics, the New York wise guys think that he's not hip and he's not cool, we went through this with Conan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Was it fair, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I think it was -- it doesn't really matter if it was fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Are you available if they decided to go in a different direction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "If money is right, everyone is available, Howard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How do you fix it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Well, I think they have to get over this period of media attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Bad management?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I think bad management -- change of management.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Lauer"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What does that tell you about what is really going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "But one reason it gave me pause is that I was able to report a couple of weeks ago on \"The Daily Beast\" that Matt Lauer had offered to step aside.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Three a month?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "We are increasingly living in a garrison state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "It's a pointless point-scoring exercise, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Well, you know, pretty harsh words about him being mean to children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["five dollars"], "ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "The solution is this, the American people would, I'm sure, be quite happy to pay five dollars each to go and see the White House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Ben Ferguson, will you always remember where you were when Bill O'Reilly publicly supported gay rights in this extraordinary manner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "You know, there's a lot of people like myself that support civil unions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson", "Bill O'Reilly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Ben, are you married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "But also are very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Let Abby Hunstman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "You're married.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abby Hunstman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Why did you not just get a civil union then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Because I believe that marriage -- and the sanctity of marriage, and what it represents, was important for me and for what I believe in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Could you imagine a situation in 2016 where the Republican candidate who takes on whoever the Democratic candidate is would be anti same-sex marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "-NONE-", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "No, what I mean is, could you imagine a Republican candidate who didn't support same-sex marriage in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "It would be -- I don't think they could actually win a general election, is my answer to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "But this must feel a bit surreal, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["two years ago"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "When did you have the germ of the idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "'ALOISIO: So, it was about two years ago, when I was 15.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 800, "question": "What was it about you, do you think, that they liked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 801, "answer": "Fundamentally, I think it came down to the idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Or are you hopeful it's going to become ever bigger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "No, I'm really enthusiastic by the opportunity at Yahoo1.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last two years"]}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "Reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "No, from my perspective, I think we have robust I.P. that we've been developing for the last two years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "You thinking of doing a new campaign, because he's worth it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "Are you single at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "No, I do have a girlfriend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "'ALOISIO: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 828, "question": "How is she feeling about the fact you're now worth 30 million dollars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 829, "answer": "I don't think that really comes into it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["30 million dollars"]}}]